[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About 95% of fresh water in the USA is underground. What is the name of the biggest source of fresh water in the USA?", "correct_answer": "The Ogallala Aquifer", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lake Superior Aquifer", "The Tampa Aquifer", "The Columbian Aquifer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This food has the same chemical as Prozac, and can put a person in a better mood.", "correct_answer": "Bananas", "incorrect_answers": ["Prunes", "Cheese", "Potatoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the alter ego of Marvel Comics fictional character Moon Knight.", "correct_answer": "Marc Spector", "incorrect_answers": ["Victor Spector", "Steve Rogers", "Douglas Ramsey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is unusual about Plutos three known moons compared to other moons in the Solar System?", "correct_answer": "They are untypically close to Pluto.", "incorrect_answers": ["They orbit Pluto at a very high speed.", "They are asteroids from another solar system attracted by Pluto and captured by gravitational forces.", "Their orbits are unusually big and elliptical."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy Adventures in Babysitting, Chris and the kids drive into Chicago to pick up Chris boyfriend.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Africa, a certain type of chimpanzees have been observed making snowballs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who makes a cameo appearance at the beginning of the movie Airplane!, as a member of the airport ground crew?", "correct_answer": "David Zucker", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Urich", "William Shatner", "Dr. Joyce Brothers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a pharmacy setting, what does ft. mean?", "correct_answer": "let it be made", "incorrect_answers": ["feet", "for tincture", "place under tongue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the Razzie Award for Worst actor for 1991?", "correct_answer": "Kevin Costner for Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves", "incorrect_answers": ["Vanilla Ice Cool as Ice", "Sylvester Stallone for Oscar", "Bruce Willis for Hudson Hawk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the Imperial soldiers want to destroy while in the AT-AT Walkers?", "correct_answer": "The Shield Generator", "incorrect_answers": ["The Rebel Base", "The Millennium Falcon", "The Hidden Bunker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a combination in chess?", "correct_answer": "A sequence of moves leading to an advantage", "incorrect_answers": ["A sequence of moves leading to zugzwang", "A sequence of moves leading to checkmate", "A sequence of moves involving a sacrifice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a red house is made out of red bricks, a black house is made out of black bricks, and a white house is made out of white bricks, what is a greenhouse made out of?", "correct_answer": "glass", "incorrect_answers": ["green bricks", "leaves", "none of the above"]}]